

Sacit KÜHEYLAN

Computer Engineer

sacit.kuheylan@yandex.com • +90 542 653 94 84

Profile

I am currently in my senior year at my Computer Engineering Degree. I have worked in various long-term projects. I am mostly interested in Low-Level Programming and I am passionate about developing software that works close to hardware level.

I especially have knowledge ablout;

- MISRA C Standards
- TCP/IP Protocols
- Network Programming
- Embedded Linux Systems

Professional Experience

09/2021 – Present Antalya, Turkey

Part Time Software Engineer, *Otkosis*

- I am responsible about developing Embedded Software for custom designed PCB's that uses ATMEL ATMEGA328 Microcontroller Unit.
- I am responsible about developing mobile application with Flutter technology in order to create MQTT communication with the Embedded Software I have developed for the company.

07/2021 – 08/2021 Istanbul, Turkey

Intern Software Engineer, Pavotek

- I was responsible about developing a C Program to communicate with a web service that using SOAP API.
- I was responsible about parsing XML responses and also modifying those responses.
- Both tasks were using SNMP at background in order to communicate.

07/2020 – 08/2020 Antalya, Turkey

Intern Software Engineer, Fiberli by PSL Electronic

 I was responsible about maintanence of CRM programs and Windows Server Administration.

Education

2017 – Present Antalya, Turkey

Computer Engineering (B.S.), Akdeniz Üniversitesi

I am in my senior year at Akdeniz University - Computer Engineering Department

Tech Stack

C Programming

Developing C Programs using native and open source libraries.

C++ Programming

Developing C++ Programs using QT Framework

Flutter

Developing native mobile applications using Flutter.